My Little Pony: Equestria Girls - Rollercoaster of Friendship is a
animation, family, music film directed by Ishi Rudell.
Rarity's friendship with Applejack is tested when Vignette Valencia
hires her as her new designer for a theme park parade.
Sunset Shimmer / Designer / Twilight Sparkle
(singing), played by Rebecca Shoichet.
Rarity / Granny Smith, played by Tabitha St. Germain.
Applejack / Rainbow Dash, played by Ashleigh Ball.
Pinkie Pie / Fluttershy, played by Andrea Libman.
Twilight Sparkle, played by Tara Strong.
Vignette Valencia, played by Tegan Moss.
My Little Pony: Equestria Girls – Forgotten Friendship (alternatively subtitled Most Likely to be Forgotten on the YouTube release) is a 2018 animated
television special within Hasbro's My Little Pony: Equestria Girls franchise, itself a spin-off of the 2010 relaunch of the My Little Pony toy line.
The special was directed by Ishi Rudell and Katrina Hadley, written and edited by Nick
Confalone, and produced by DHX Media Vancouver for Hasbro Studios in the United States.
Premiered on Discovery Family (a joint venture between Discovery Communications and Hasbro) on February 17, 2018, it is the first one-hour Equestria Girls special,
preceding Rollercoaster of Friendship (released later in July), Spring Breakdown (2019), Sunset's Backstage Pass (2019), and Holidays Unwrapped (2019).
The film explores themes of friendship, fashion
designer, theme park, social media.